来たの 遅かったじゃない
You're here? It's about time...
Um... Kashiwazaki?
えっと 柏崎
星奈って呼びなさい
Call me "Sena"!
あんたあの狐女のこと名前で呼んでたでしょう
You call that fox woman
by her first name, don't you?
あたしが名字だと
If you use my family name, it's like
I take second place in your head.
あんたの中であたしの方が優先順位下みたいじゃない
Got it...
わかったよ せ 星奈
S-Sena...
Let's begin the Neighbors Club activity.
隣人部の活動を始める
Hey, Mikazu...
なあ 三日月
It's Yozora!
夜空だ
Yo... zora...
夜 空
Hey, what is our club activity?
なあ 活動って何だ
結局 友達をつくるなんて簡単にできる
I mean, there's no way
we can simply make friends...
友達をつくるには ゲームだ
Video games are one way to make friends!
WANAWANA
Gutto Good hajiketeru
グッと Good 弾ける
Angai nandai hamatten jan
案外なんだい ハマってんじゃん
Hito mishiri shiteru hima ni hajimeyou!
人見知りしてる暇に 始めよう
Tomodachi tsukucchatte asonjatte Yeh!
友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah!
"Haganai"
Kuuru ni miete, jitsu wa chou sabishii
クールに見えて 実は超寂しい
(Mosou nara bai, bai, bai
Shinyuu nara inai, inai, inai, inai)
妄想ならバイバイバイ
親友なら いないいないいないいない
Nani fujiyuu naku, dakedo tarinai
何不自由なく だけど足りない
(Riajuu kara tooi, tooi, tooi?
Shinyuu nara inai, inai, inai, inai)
リア充から遠い遠い遠い
親友なら いないいないいないいない
Zannen doushi de atsumattara
残念同士で 集まったら
Ah- yosou ga dekinai
Ah- 予想が出来ない 展開の 地雷を踏んだ
Tenkai no jirai wo funda!
SOWASOWA
絶対絶対覗きたい
Zettai, zettai nozokitai
Koukai hyakkai shitakunaitte
後悔100回したくないって
Tsumannai puraido nante
sutekicchatte furikicchatte
つまんない プライドなんて
捨てきっちゃって 振りきっちゃって
Zannen kannen shite mitara,
angai nandai hamatten jan
残念観念してみたら
案外なんだいハマってんじゃん
Butsukatte, dogimagi atte, mitsukeyou!
ぶつかって どぎまぎ合って 見つけよう
Tomodachi tsukucchatte asonjatte Yeh!
友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah
Zettai, zettai nozokitai
絶対絶対覗きたい
You! Sutekicchatte furikicchatte
YOU！ 捨てきっちゃって 振りきっちゃって
Yes! Doudai? Doudai, sokontoko
Yes！ どーだいどーだいそこんとこ
本字幕由诸神卖萌组(kamigami.org)出品 仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
---诸神卖萌组---
日听：安少   翻译: 银苹果   校对：喵儿 小草爱吃梨
时间轴：nono   后期：Maize
"There's No God in the Electric World"
I'm telling you, only kids
would be taken in by that!
だからそんなので釣られるのは子供くらいだって
You're naïve, Kodaka.
The majority of recent games... are on this!
甘いな小鷹
最近のゲームの主流は これだ
Playing States Portable.
プレイングステイツポータブルだ
PSP, right? My little sister has one, too.
PSPだろう うちの妹も持ってる
When I went to a family
restaurant by myself last night...
昨日の夜1人でファミレスに行ってたら
You went to a family restaurant alone?!
1人でファミレス
Shut up!
うるさい
There were four high school
students at the table behind me
そこで後ろの席にいた4人の高校生が
who were having a good time playing this.
楽しそうにこれをやっていた
"Monster Hunting Portable"
who were having a good time playing this.
Oh, Monster Hunting, huh?
あ 「モン狩り」か
You know it?
知ってるの
It's an action game where you hunt
monsters and animals in a fantasy world.
ファンタジー世界でモンスターや動物を狩るアクションゲームだ
In this game, you can play
cooperatively with other people.
このゲームでは他の人間と協力して遊ぶことができる
If you're good, other players
will come to depend on you,
うまくなれば他のプレイヤーに頼られるから
and while playing, you can become friends.
ゲームをやるうちに仲良くなれるというわけだ
You can exchange items too, and
it's easy to make opportunities to talk.
アイテムの交換もできて
話しかけるきっかけも作りやすい
In other words, our club activity
will be building our skill at this game...
つまり部活でこのゲームの腕を磨いたり
...getting items...
- Hey!
アイテムを手に入れて
友達を作ろうってわけか
...and then trying to make friends?
- Don't touch it! You'll leave a smudge!
触るな 油がつく
I'm not that oily!
あたしそんな脂ぎってないわよ
- Are they even listening?
- Shut up, Fatty Meat!
って 話し聞いてる
黙れ 油肉
- And so, next Monday,
bring a PSP and Monster Hunting.
- Why, you...
というわけで
来週の月曜日 PSPとモン狩を持ってくること
O-Okay...
And so, the following Monday...
そして次の月曜日
You've practiced using the
controls and everything, right?
操作とかは予習してあるな
Yeah.
I was busy, but I fiddled with it a little bit.
ふん 忙しいかったけど
ちょっとだけ試しに遊んであげたわ
Although it's just a game. Kid's stuff...
まあ所詮はゲームなんてお子様のお遊びだけどね
Kodaka and Milk Cow, what are your ranks?
小鷹と乳牛のゲームランクは
Still at one...
俺はまだ1 全然敵が倒せなくてな
I haven't been able to
take down any of the enemies.
ふっ 私は3だ
I'm three.
Three?! Wow!
3 すごいな
I'm six!
あたしは6
Six?!
６！？
That's the top rank!
それって確か 最高ランク
ゲームまで天才的だなんて
Guess I'm a prodigy even when it comes
to video games. How perfect can I get?!
あたしってどこまで完壁なのかしら
I thought you said
you'd only played it a little...
さっきちょっとだけって言ってなかったか
どんだけやりこんでるんだよ
How much time did you spend on it?
H-Hardly any time at all!
べ べつにやりこんでなんかないわよ
プレイ時間見せてみろ肉
Let me see your playing time, Meat!
あ ちょっと 勝手に見ないでよ
Hey!
I didn't give you permission to look!
"Playing Time: 53 hours, 27 minutes"
What?! 53 hours?!
なに 53時間だと
And the outfit is cute...
しかもなんか装備も可愛いし
Too cocky for half-baked Meat!
生焼け肉のくせに生意気だ
いたた
Oww!
なにすんのよ
What do you think you're doing?!
Hey!
お前 目の下にクマがあるな
You've got bags under your eyes...
そ そんなわけないでしょう
I-I do not!
After we went home on Friday, you
spent the whole weekend playing, didn't you?!
さては 金曜家に帰ってから土日の間ずっとコレやってただろう
A-A bobcat always devotes
itself to whatever it's doing,
し 獅子はたかがモンスター狩りにすら全力を注ぐのよ
even if it's just Monster Hunting!
A boobcat?
乳
Bobcat!
獅子
Oh...
Cryin' out loud!
ったく
Okay, let's start the game. I'll host.
さあ あたしがホストで ゲーム始めるわよ
I'll let you two warm up by taking
on an easygoing quest, so get ready.
肩慣らしで手頃なクエスト受けてあげるから準備しなさい
なんだかんだ言って 真面目に部活に取り込んでんだよな
When all's said and done, she's
making a serious effort for this club.
Okay, let's go!
それじゃ 行くわよ
Sorry to keep you waiting!
お待たせ
What's with that get-up?!
なんだあの姿は
What do you expect?! I'm still a beginner!
しょうがないだろ
まだ始めたばっかなんだから
It's not the equipment,
but the entire character!
装備じゃなくてキャラ自体のことだ
It's sad how much it doesn't
resemble you in the slightest.
悲しいくらい本人と似てないな
Does this mean you wanna be a
long-haired foreigner like that, Kodaka?
小鷹はこういうロン毛の外人になりたいわけ
And your character name,
"Hawk," talk about cheesy!
キャラの名前がホークっていうのもベタベタよね
"Hawk"
Leave me alone!
ほっとけ ゲームなんだからちょっとくらい現実と違ってもいいだろ
This is a game, so it can be
a little bit different from reality!
A little bit?!
ちょっと？
All right, let's go hunting!
さあ 狩りへ出発だ
- Let's go hunting for the boss right away!
- Cut it out!
さっさとボスを狩りに行くぞ
Where should we go first?
まずはどこに向かうか
"Night has lost all her might."
はぁ？！　なにするんだ肉
Huh?! What the hell was that, Meat?
Oopsie! I goofed up with the controls.
ごめんごめん　ちょっと操作をミスしちゃったわね
Now pull yourself together
so we can go hunting.
さ 気を取り直して狩りに出かけましょう
Could a rank six player really
make a mistake like that?
ランク６のヤツがいまさらそんなミス
Don't tell me she spent tens of
hours of playing for that moment?!
まさか このために何十時間も
Well, I can't blame you for
making a mistake with the controls...
操作ミスなら仕方ないな
Shall we go?
じゃあ 行くか
よし
There!
いきなり何すんのよ
What the hell was that about?!
Whoops. I pushed the wrong button.
あー ボタン押し間違えた
You were clearly aiming at me!
今のどう考えても狙ったでしょう
I was not. I wish you would stop
with your incessant false accusations!
狙ってない
事実無根の言いがかりはやめてほしいな
You dirty, lowdown...
こんのー
Hey, here it comes!
おい 来たぞ
I'll easily kick this guy's ass!
こんなのあたしが蹴散らしてあげる
ふん　蜥蜴の分際であたしに逆らうなんて百億年早
It'll be a hundred years before
some lizard can stand up to me...
K-Knockout drug?!
睡眠薬？
Hey, Yozora...
おい 夜空
Kaboom!
せい
"Objective achieved."
"Quest Completed"
Yes! I killed it!
よし 今度は仕留めた
What?!
なんですって
I was trying to give you backup,
but used a little too much force. Sorry.
いや 掩護しようとしたのだがな
不可抗力だ 悪いな
You were obviously targeting me!
どう見てもあたし狙いじゃない
Look, this is co-op play,
so cooperate, would ya?!
なあ 協力プレイなんだから
ちゃんと協力しようぜ
ふん　そうだな 次の狩りではもっと協力してやろう
You're right.
On the next hunt, I'll cooperate even more.
I'll seriously cooperate, too!
あたしも本気で協力するわ
覚悟しなさい
Brace yourself.
And after that, the true hunting began...
そして このあと　真の狩りが始まった
It's disgusting to see meat moving around.
肉が動き回るなど不快だ
I'm gonna turn you into ground meat.
挽肉にしてやろう
Talk about "trash talk"...
ゴミカスの分際で生意気よ
Now hold still and let me hunt you!
大人しくあたしに狩られなさい
Silence, Meat!
黙れ肉
Shut up, stupid fox!
うるさいバカギツネ
ほ ドクライト ラッキー
Dogrite! Lucky!
Act like the trash you are and lick my boots!
カスはカスらしく 跪いて靴を舐めなさい
Shut your mouth and die, Meat!
黙ってさっさとくたばれ 肉
H-Help me!!
助けてくれ
悪い 力尽きちまった…
Sorry. I died...
I only really feel alive
when I'm killing someone!
人を殺すときだけ生きていると実感できる
I'm gonna rip out your intestines and
cram 'em down your throat, stupid fox!
ブッた切られて腸をブチ撒けろバカキツネ
Die!
死ね
- Don't duck, idiot!
- Become minced meat!
避けんな バカ
挽肉になれ
"Your time is up."
"Quest Failed"
ふん やっぱりゲームは駄目だな
I guess video games aren't a good idea.
We were just wasting time.
無駄な時間を過ごしちゃったわ
だいたい 最近の携帯ゲーム機は
And I don't like that portable
game systems these days
通信プレイありきというのが気に入らない
are all about multiplayer games.
Why should I have to play
the game with other people?
どうして他人と一緒にゲームをやらなきゃいけないんだ
Then what was the point
of today's club activity?!
それじゃ今日の部活の意味が…
Exactly.
まったくその通りね
Something's wrong when you
have to worry about other people,
ゲームの世界でまで他人に気を遣わなきゃいけないなんてどうかしてるわ
even in some game world!
Totally!
まったくだ
When have you two ever
worried about somebody else?
お前らいつ他人に気を遣った
N-Nothing.
なんでもありません
Where should we stop in today?
今日はどこ寄ってく
Let's see...
そうだなー
How was Monster Hunting last night?
夕べモン狩りどうだった
I took down Jinrou, but it
didn't bring down any imperial wrath.
ジンロウガ倒したけど 逆鱗出ないんだよな
Even though I've got plenty of tail...
尻尾は余ってんのにさあ
よーし
All right!
If you've got extra loot, share it with me!
尻尾余ってんだったら分けてよ
Okay.
オッケー
H-Hey...
なあ
I'm playing Monster Hunting too, see...
俺もモン狩やってるんだけどさ
If you've got "Dosjagira's Scarf,"
ドスジャギラの襟巻き持ってたら
would you trade me something for it?
交換してくれないか
もちろんいいよ
Of course!
I-Is there anything else you could use?!
ほ 他にもなにかほしいのある
I'll give you anything!
何でもあげるから
そうか 悪いな
Really? I'd appreciate it!
By the following day, a rumor
had spread through the whole class
翌日には俺が白昼堂々教室でカツアゲしたという噂が
that I pulled a shakedown
in our room in broad daylight.
クラス中に広まっていた
What's that?
なんだそれ
Ignorant, as expected of a Yankee.
ヤンキーだけあって無知ね
これはテレビジョンとプレイングステイツという文明の利器よ
They're two modern conveniences
known as a TV and a Playing States system.
電気で動くわ
They run on electricity.
未開人か俺は
What do you think I am, a barbarian?
I meant, what are they doing in the club room?
なんで部室にそんなものをことだ
They're here so we can play a game, duh!
ゲームをやるために決まってるじゃない
一体どうやってそんなでかい物を
How the hell did you get that TV in here?
I mean, why bother bringing
it all the way to school?
てかなんでわざわざ学校にまで持ってきてやるんだよ
This time, it isn't a crap
game like Monster Hunting,
モン狩りみたいなくそゲームじゃなくて
but one that looked useful to the club,
so I took the trouble to bring it here.
部活に役立ちそうなゲームを見つけたから
わざわざ持ってきてあげたのよ
Be grateful, you pieces of trash.
感謝しなさいクズども
Silence, Meat. You'll make my coffee go bad.
黙れ肉 コーヒーがまずくなる
あたしが持ってきたティーセット 勝手に使わないでよ
I never gave you permission
to use the tea set I brought over!
Sparkling School Life... 7?
きらめきスクールライフ７
Is that one of those so-called "gal games"?
いわゆるギャルゲーってやつか
It's a game that's a
perfect fit for our club, right?
部の活動に相応しいゲームでしょう
True, it could be good for
conversation skill practice.
たしかに 他人と会話する練習になるかもしれないな
But isn't this aimed at guys?
でもこれって男向けじゃないか
I'm sure there are games aimed more at girls,
確か女の子向けでイケメンと仲良くなるヤツもあったと
where you try to befriend good-looking men...
Huh? What's the point of
making friends with guys?
はあ 男なんかと仲良くなってどうすんの
So it's like that, huh?
さいですか
"Sparkling School Life 7"
"Sparkling School Life 7."
"Start from the beginning"
"Continue game"
"Bonus" "Options" "Install"
"Name"
か か 柏崎
Ka... Ka... Kashi... wazaki...
おい肉 なんで勝手にお前の名前にしてるんだ
Hey, Meat! What's the idea of using your name?!
Excuse me?!
Since I'm the public face of this
club, you should put in my name.
ここは部の代表である私の名前を入れるべきだ
And when exactly did you become
the face of this club, stupid fox?!
いつからあんたが部の代表になったのよ馬鹿ギツネ
Hey, the main character is a guy,
so how about using my name?
なあ 主人公は男だから俺の名前で
Forget about it!
却下
The only time you two are in harmony...
こういう時は息ぴったりだな
Well, Sena's the one who brought the
game here, so shouldn't we use her name?
まぁ　ゲーム持ってきたのは星奈なんだから
名前くらい星奈に譲るのは妥当じゃないか
Fine, whatever.
しょうがないな
Kodaka understands.
わかってるじゃない小鷹
えっと　柏崎せ　せ…
Let's see, Kashiwazaki Se... Se... Se...
I changed my mind.
やっぱり気に入らない
There.
えい
For crying out loud! What are you doing, stupid?
もう 何すんのよ馬鹿
僕の名前は柏崎せもぼぬめ
"My name is Kashiwazaki Semoponume."
何よせもぼぬめって
What's "Semoponume"?!
I think it's a nice name.
まあ 結構いい名前じゃないか
いっそ改名したらどうだ
Why don't you change your real name to that?
星奈という名前は口に出すだけでムカムカしてくるし
After all, the name "Sena" makes me
sick to my stomach every time I say it.
よう せもぼぬめ
"Yo, Semoponume!"
"This guy's name is Suzuki Masaru.
We've been best friends since middle school."
こいつの名前は鈴木マサル
中学時代からの親友だ
What the hell?! He already has a best friend?!
馬鹿な 既に親友がいるだと
なのにまだ友達がほしいとか言ってるのか この男は
And he's got the balls to
say he still wants friends?!
小鷹顔が怖い ていうか キモイ
Kodaka, that's a scary look!
Or more like gross!
充実した学園生活を送るには
"The best way to lead
a fulfilling high school life
is to get cozy with a cute girl!"
カワウィー女の子と仲良くなるのが一番
You're a player, but you do
know what you're talking about.
いいこと言うわ チャラ男のくせに
まさにあたしはそういう友達がほしいのよ
I mean, that's exactly
the kind of friend I want!
"Nice to meet you. I'm Fujibayashi Akari.
はじめまして 私 藤林あかり
入学したばっかりで不安だったんだけど
I was nervous about starting at a new school,
but I'm relieved to sit next to such a nice guy.
隣がいい人そうでよかった
これから仲良くしてね 柏崎くん
Let's be friends, okay, Kashiwazaki-kun?"
"1) 'Nice to meet you, Akari-chan! '"
"2) 'Oh, it's nice to meet you, Fujibayashi-san.'"
"3) 'What a pushy broad. Get lost! '"
どう答えるか選べってか
Oh, you choose how the guy answers...
Number 3!
３だね
Why 3?!
なんで3 一番ありえねえだろ
"1) 'Nice to meet you, Akari-chan! '"
"2) 'Oh, it's nice to meet you, Fujibayashi-san.'"
"3) 'What a pushy broad. Get lost! '"
It's the most unlikely one!
入学初日にいきなり知らない男に声をかけてくるような女が
There's no way you can trust a girl
who suddenly starts chatting
to some guy she doesn't know
on the first day of school!
信用できるわけないじゃない
Yep. I'm sure she says the same
exact thing to all of the guys in class.
ああ きっとこの女 クラスの男全員に同じことを言ってるぞ
Aw, come on. She looks
like a serious girl, doesn't she?
いやいやいや 真面目そうな娘じゃないか
こういうのに限って本当はビッチなのだ
That's what she looks like
now, but she's really a bitch.
There's one in every class.
クラスに一人はいるだろう
A girl who looks pure and innocent,
清純そうな見た目で裏では男を食いまくってる女
but is actually running
around with all the guys.
There's someone like that in our class?
いるのかそんなやつ
きっといる
I'm sure. It says on the Net that high
school girls are all bitches these days.
最近のＪＫはビッチばっかりってネットに書いてあったし
You're one of those
"high school girls these days," too...
お前もその最近のＪＫなわけだが
Okay, so we agree on number 3.
それじゃ 3で決まりね
"What a pushy broad. Get lost!"
馴れ馴れしい女だな 消えろ
"S-Sorry, Kashiwazaki-kun.
ご ごめんね 柏崎くん
確かに初対面なのに馴れ馴れしかったかも
As it is our first time meeting,
I may have been too forward...
I'll be more careful from now on,
so I hope you're not mad at me."
今度から気をつけるから 気を悪くしないでね
ごめんな 藤林さん
I'm sorry, Fujibayashi-san.
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
So it looks like you choose your actions,
行動を選んでバラメーターを上げると
and if you meet the right parameters,
you'll encounter girls, right?
女の子との出会いが発生するみたいだな
It's a rough world for guys
実力がない者は女子と知り合うことさえできないとは世知辛いな
who don't even have enough
merit to go out with a girl.
Just like reality.
まるで現実のようだ
とにかく 学力が低いのは論外ね
Anyway, having low test
scores is out of the question.
Let's start with having him study.
まずは勉強をやらせるわよ
Good idea. I hate guys
who are cerebrally challenged.
そうだな 頭の悪い男は嫌いだ
The more he studies, the smarter he gets?
勉強すればするだけ伸びるとは
How stupid was this guy at the beginning?
こいつは最初どれだけバカだったのだ
Well, it is a game...
いや そこはゲームだし
あ 誰がきたぞ
Somebody's here.
あ すみません
"Oh, sorry..."
"1) Say 'No, I'm sorry,' and let her have the book."
"2) Say 'I had this book first!'
take it, and walk away."
Another choice?
また選択肢
I'm sure they'll go with 2...
どうせまた2か
Which one are you gonna do?
で どっちにする
1だね
え なんで
Why?!
Instead of reading books, you'd better
use your time to study, Semoponume.
本なんて読んでる暇があったら勉強しろせもぽぬめ
I'm aiming for a 200 in
academic ability by the next test,
次のテストまでに学力200を目指してるんだから
so don't you slack off, trash!
サボってんじゃないわよクズ
Of course...
だよな
こっちこそごめん
"No, I'm sorry."
ありがとうございます
"Thank you!
あの よろしければ
Um, if you don't mind, may I have your name?"
お名前を教えていただけませんか
"Sure. I'm Kashiwazaki
Semoponume from class D."
いいよ 僕はD組の柏崎せもぽぬめ
柏崎せもぽぬめさん
"Kashiwazaki Semoponume-san...
いいお名前ですね
That's a nice name."
What terrible taste...
なんという残念な感性 こわ
It's scary...
"You are now able to ask
Nagata Yukiko out on a date."
For now, I'm thinking of
being friends with this girl.
とりあえずこの子と友達になってみようと思うけど
Do you have a problem with that?
文句ないわね
She's a lot better than that Fujibayashi bitch.
ビッチの藤林よりはるかにマシか まあいいだろう
Go ahead.
"Yukiko..."
有希子
"Yes?"
はい
はー 可愛いわこの子
This girl is so cute!
Really cute!
ほんと可愛い
女の子が自分を慕ってくれるのって最高
There's nothing better
than having a girl adore you!
ふん まあ割といいやつじゃないか
She's actually a nice girl.
有希子 一緒に帰りましょう
"Yukiko. Let's walk home together."
いや
"No."
ごめんなさい
"I'm sorry!"
W-Why?! What's wrong, Yukiko?
な なんで どうしたの有希子
長田有希子が急に冷たくなったのはこれが原因か
I guess this was the reason
Nagata Yukiko suddenly became cold...
What do you mean?!
どういうことよ
Every time you meet Fujibayashi-san,
you've treated her like dirt, right?
お前 藤林さんに会うたびにひどい扱いばっかしてただろう
ある女の子に嫌われると悪い噂が流れて
When one girl hates you,
she spreads unfavorable rumors
which cause a chain reaction,
連鎖的に他の女の子にも悪い印象を与えるらしい
making all the other girls
get a bad impression of you.
In other words, Yukiko
doesn't like me anymore
つまりあたしが有希子に嫌われたのは
藤林があたしの悪口を学校中に触れ回ってるからなのね
because Fujibayashi has been going around
bad-mouthing me all over the school, huh?!
That rotten bitch!
あんの腐れビッチ
いや そういうことじゃなくて
I don't think that's how it happened...
ここには 評判が悪くなったら早く謝って仲直りしようって書いてあるぞ
It says here, " If you get a bad reputation,
quickly apologize and make up."
Huh?! Why do I have to
apologize to that frickin' bitch?!
はあ なんであたしがあのクソ女に謝らないといけないの
仲直りもなにも あの雌豚と仲直くなった覚えなんてないわ
"Make up," my ass! I don't remember
ever being on friendly terms with that sow!
I agree!
同感だ
自分が悪いわけでもないのに
It's not our fault!
By no means should we bow
down to that stupid woman
勝手に話しかけてきて勝手に傷ついたなどとぬかす
who started talking to us
and got hurt on her own!
バカ女に頭を下げるなんてまっぴらだ
We agree, huh?
意見が合ったわね
あたしは絶対に譲らない
I'm definitely not caving on this one.
それに有希子ならきっと誤解だってわかってくれるはずよ
And I'm sure Yukiko will understand
that it's all a misunderstanding!
Yeah!
"1) Give up on Yukiko."
"2) Believe in Yukiko!"
Yukiko, I...
有希子　あたし
I'm sorry!
ごめんなさい
さよなら
Goodbye!
Wait!
待って
I-I had faith in Yukiko...
ゆ 有希子　信じてたのに
Seriously? How emotionally
involved is she in this game?
マジかよ どんだけ感情移入してんだ
Hey! Where are you going?
おい どこ行く気だ お前は
I'm gonna kill Fujibayashi Akari!
藤林あかり ブチ殺す
だ 大丈夫か
A-Are you okay?
Yukiko!!
有希子ー！
Good morning!
おはよー
Kodaka! Kodaka!
小鷹 小鷹
こっち こっち
Over here!
Here!
はい
それ貸したげるから　帰ったらすぐやりなさいよね
I'm letting you borrow that,
so use it as soon as you get home!
特に藤林あかりの三年目のイベントなんてマジ泣けるんだから
The third-year event with
Fujibayashi Akari is especially moving!
You're the one who kept calling
Fujibayashi Akari a bitch and a sow yesterday!
お前昨日散々 藤林あかりのことをビッチだの雌豚だのって
Don't talk like that about Akari!
あかりのことを悪く言わないで
あれ
Huh?
いい あかりはね
Listen, Akari has been all on her own
since she lost both her parents as a kid.
幼い頃に両親を亡くして一人ぼっちで苦労してきたの
She's been through a lot!
それでも世間を恨むことなく
And yet, she doesn't hold
a grudge against the world,
but shares a warm smile with everyone.
周囲に笑顔を振りまいてるのよ
さいですか
Is that right?
Also! Make sure you capture Yukiko!
あと 有希子も絶対攻略すること
ていうか
Actually, Aina, Miho, Natsumi, Mizuki, Karen...
アイナも美帆も菜摘も観月も可憐も
みんないい子なのよ
They're all good girls!
お前 昨日帰ってから 全員攻略したのかよ
After going home yesterday,
you conquered all of them?!
Of course!
もちろんよ あんたも絶対全員のエンディングを見るべきだわ
You'd definitely better watch
the endings of all of them, too!
わかった
Got it?!
Well, I'll try it, if I'm in the mood...
まあ 気が向いたらやってみるよ
Not good enough! Do it,
whether you're in the mood or not!
ダメ 気が向いたらじゃなくて絶対やること
これは義務よ
It's your duty.
「きらスク」は全ての国民がプレイすべき作品だわ
Sparkling School is a work
that all people should play!
これはただのゲームなんかじゃない
It's not just a game!
In a word, it's...
言うなればそう
人生 かしらね
...life, I suppose.
Oh, no! Class is gonna start!
いけない 授業が始まっちゃう
絶対やるのよ
You'd better do it!
いけね
Uh oh!
Neighbors Club Record:
隣人部 活動記録
Sena became friends with seven girls.
星奈が七人の女の子と仲良くなった
Two-dimensional girls...
二次元で
Aa, nounai souzou risou no genjitsu touhi
あー 脳內 想像理想の 現実逃避
Ima sara docchi datte ikkedo... tomodachi zukuri
今更どっちだっていっけど 友達作り
Hitori sabishii yatsu da to
sagesumu shisen ga ki ni naru
一人寂しい奴だと蔑む 視線が気になる
De, uwattsura dake atsumattara...
で 上っ面だけ集まったら
Sore de ii to omotte iru uchi ni~
それでいいと 思っているうちに
Are yo are yo to toujou, sorotte
あれよあれよと登場 揃って 破天荒な奴らに
Hatenkou na yatsura ni
Maipeesu midasarete yuku
マイペース 乱されてゆく 頭くる！特に憎っくき肉
Atama kuru! Toku ni nikukkuki niku!
Watashi no mune, hisoka
ni asette yuujou fudan kimi de
私の胸秘かに焦って 優柔不斷気味で
My heart tsutaerarenai
My heart 伝えられない 殘念なのは 私なのか
Zannen na no wa watashi na no ka?
Moya moya wo kakiwake Today!
もやもやを かきわけ Today！
Okizari ni sareta otome
gokoro ano hi kara kuyande iru
置き去りにされた 乙女心 あの日から悔やんでいる
Hayaku mitsuke dashite, maigo no kokoro
早く見つけ出して 迷子のココロ
知っているか 肉
Meat, did you know?
If you clear a "gal game"
ギャルゲーを徹夜でクリアすると
in the middle of the night,
you'll be brainwashed by it.
その人間の脳波がギャルゲーに支配されてしまうということを
え マジで
Seriously?!
People whose brainwaves
are controlled by gal games
脳波がギャルゲーに支配されてしまった人間は
lose their normal sense of judgment
正常な判断ができなくなってしまい
友達ができなくなってしまうという
and aren't able to make any friends, it's said!
やめてよ
Stop it!
On top of that, their hair
turns a stupid blond color,
しかも髪が間抜けな金髪になったり
the fat around their chest
increases, and they turn into cows!
無駄に胸の脂肪が増えて乳牛になってしまったり
それホントなの
Is that true?!
Of course it's a lie!
もちろん嘘だ
夜空のアホ
Yozora, you're an idiot!
You're the idiot!
アホはお前だ
次回 「市民プールはフラグがない」
Next time: "There are No
Flags at the Swimming Pool."
"Next time: There are No
Flags at the Swimming Pool"
ん なんだプールって
Why "pool"?